Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, Residence Division, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, Co-ed Inquiries, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, Correspondence on new building, 1954-1957 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, Local, 1968-1969 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, National, 1965-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Lambda Nu, Switch to Co-ed, 1968-1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Omicron Delta Kappa, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Beta Kappa, 1966-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Delta Theta, 1957-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Delta Theta, 1967-1972 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Delta Theta Steering Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Gamma Delta, 1956-1965 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Gamma Delta, 1965-1967 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Gamma Delta, 1968-1971 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Gamma Delta, Local Issue, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Kappa Psi, 1961-1969 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Kappa Psi, 1970-1972 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities: Phi Kappa Sigma, 1952-1969 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Phi Kappa Sigma, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Phi Sigma Kappa, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Phi Sigma Kappa, 1966-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Phi Sigma Kappa House Information, 1957-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1965-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, 1959-1963 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, 1964 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, 1965-1969 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, Suspension I, 1965 Jan-Apr (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, Suspension II, 1965 May-Dec (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi, Suspension, S.U. Press Releases, 1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Chi Omega, 1967-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Sigma Nu, 1953-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Chi, 1952-1967 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Chi, 1965-1970 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Chi, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Delta Chi, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Delta Chi, 1966-1970 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Delta Chi, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Xi, 1961-1969 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Theta Xi, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Alpha Phi, 1969-1970 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Alpha Phi, 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Psi, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Psi (Confidential), 1963 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Psi (Confidential), 1964 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Psi, 1966-1969 (Box 13)
  - Fraternities: Zeta Psi, 1970-1971 (Box 13)